<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Macro Snap</string>
    <string-array name="armband_names">
        <item>Grizz</item>
        <item>Panda</item>
        <item>Ice Bear</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gesture_types">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Fist</item>
        <item>Wrist Supination</item>
        <item>Wrist Pronation</item>
        <item>Wrist Up (Extension)</item>
        <item>Wrist Down (Flexion)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="calib_start">To start, adjust the armband on your forearm with FSR sensors placed in the locations shown in the diagram. When you have adjusted the position of the armband, press \'START SCANNING\' and maintain resting position for a few seconds then click the UI button on the armband to start calibration.</string>
    <string-array name="calib_descriptions">
        <item>First, we will calibration your finger snap which is used to trigger gestures. When prompted by the haptic, snap your finger once. Click the UI button when you are ready. After completing 3 snaps, press the UI button to move on.</item>
        <item>Next, we will perform gesture calibration. 5 gestures will be calibrated in total and the best 3 are used. \nFor the first gesture, snap your finger then clench your fist when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until a 2nd haptic feedback ends and return to resting position then repeat 5 times. \nWe recommend a minimum of 5 repetitions for each gesture, you can perform more for more accurate detection. When you are done at least 5 repetitions, press the UI button to move on to the next gesture. \nIf you made a mistake in your gesture recording and would like to restart the calibration for this gesture, hold the UI button for 1s.</item>
        <item>For the second gesture, snap your finger then supinate your wrist (turn palm facing up) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until a 2nd haptic feedback ends and return to resting position then repeat 5 times. \nWe recommend a minimum of 5 repetitions for each gesture, you can perform more for more accurate detection. When you are done at least 5 repetitions, press the UI button to move on to the next gesture. \nIf you made a mistake in your gesture recording and would like to restart the calibration for this gesture, hold the UI button for 1s.</item>
        <item>For the third gesture, snap your finger then pronate your wrist (turn palm facing down) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until a 2nd haptic feedback ends and return to resting position then repeat 5 times. \nWe recommend a minimum of 5 repetitions for each gesture, you can perform more for more accurate detection. When you are done at least 5 repetitions, press the UI button to move on to the next gesture. \nIf you made a mistake in your gesture recording and would like to restart the calibration for this gesture, hold the UI button for 1s.</item>
        <item>For the fourth gesture, snap your finger then extend your wrist (fingers pointing upwards) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until a 2nd haptic feedback ends and return to resting position then repeat 5 times. \nWe recommend a minimum of 5 repetitions for each gesture, you can perform more for more accurate detection. When you are done at least 5 repetitions, press the UI button to move on to the next gesture. \nIf you made a mistake in your gesture recording and would like to restart the calibration for this gesture, hold the UI button for 1s.</item>
        <item>For the last gesture, snap your finger then flex your wrist (fingers pointing downwards) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until a 2nd haptic feedback ends and return to resting position then repeat 5 times. \nWe recommend a minimum of 5 repetitions for each gesture, you can perform more for more accurate detection. When you are done at least 5 repetitions, press the UI button to finish. \nIf you made a mistake in your gesture recording and would like to restart the calibration for this gesture, hold the UI button for 1s.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="calib_images">
        <item>snap</item>
        <item>fist</item>
        <item>supination</item>
        <item>pronation</item>
        <item>extension</item>
        <item>flexion</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>