<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Macro Snap</string>
    <string-array name="gesture_types">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Fist</item>
        <item>Wrist Supination</item>
        <item>Wrist Pronation</item>
        <item>Wrist Up (Extension)</item>
        <item>Wrist Down (Flexion)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="calib_start">To start, put on your armband with FSR sensors placed in the locations shown in the diagram. When you have adjusted the position of the armband, press \'START SCANNING\' and then click the UI button on the armband to start calibration.</string>
    <string-array name="calib_descriptions">
        <item>First, we will calibration your finger snap which is used to trigger gestures. When prompted by the haptic, snap your finger once. Click the UI button to start.</item>
        <item>Next, we will perform gesture calibration. 5 gestures will be calibrated in total and the best 3 are used. \nFor the first gesture, snap your finger then clench your wrist when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until another haptic feedback is provided and repeat 5 times.</item>
        <item>For the second gesture, snap your finger then supinate your fist (turn palm facing up) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until another haptic feedback is provided and repeat 5 times.</item>
        <item>For the third gesture, snap your finger then pronate your fist (turn palm facing down) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until another haptic feedback is provided and repeat 5 times.</item>
        <item>For the fourth gesture, snap your finger then extend your fist (pointing upwards) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until another haptic feedback is provided and repeat 5 times.</item>
        <item>For the last gesture, snap your finger then flex your fist (pointing downwards) when prompted by the haptic. Hold the gesture until another haptic feedback is provided and repeat 5 times.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="calib_images">
        <item>snap</item>
        <item>fist</item>
        <item>supination</item>
        <item>pronation</item>
        <item>extension</item>
        <item>flexion</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>